You just said something that's like very important can't be dogmatic when you're talking about vaccines or about anything.
Yes it is good to keep an open mind isn't it and be flexible and look at a 360 degree view of things rather than your tunnel vision
and what you're indoctrinated into isn't it?
Yeah and especially if you know that indoctrination has been on purpose and profitable.
One of the great things about your book is first of all your book is called dissolving illusions.
I know I've talked about on the podcast a bunch of times but you also highlight a lot of things that we know are beneficial
that somehow or another get lumped into nonsense like even cinnamon.
the joe rogan experience train by day joe rogan podcast by night all day
what's up what's up man good to see you good to see you uh so i guess we just get right into it
the last case that we talked about we had a very unfortunate incident happen after the podcast
about a month later yeah uh the gentleman beheaded somebody allegedly yes
allegedly there's a lot of allegedly's but yeah there's so many crazy things that case
the craziest thing was him uh trying to fool the security cameras with a wig
like i guess he didn't know how high resolution cameras had gotten over the 25 years that he was
in jail i mean apparently there's a lot he didn't know the only reason
i say allegedly is because um i'd be a bit of a hypocrite if i started calling him guilty um
before he has a trial but of course based on the surveillance um it doesn't look good