It's Tuesday, April 8th, here's what's happening right now on CNN this morning.
I have great respect for China, but they can't do this.
President Trump threatens to escalate his trade war with China, issuing them an ultimatum
and a deadline.
The China does not appear to be backing down, plus our team will get to work tomorrow to
deport these heinous, violent foreign terrorists.
The White House can resume rapid deportations, but there's a catch, new rules from the
Supreme Court, also.
This is the highest I've seen the water in my lifetime.
The flooding danger is not over as deadly storms leave some communities under water.
And in three short years, we got the University of Florida's basketball program back where
it belongs, which is winning national championships.
The Gators' Trump, Florida rallies past Houston to win the title, how they pulled off a comeback
in the final seconds.
It's 6am here on the east coast, here's a live look at Cincinnati, where communities around
the Ohio River could still see some more flooding threat today.
Good morning, everybody, I'm Audit Cornish, I want to thank you for waking up with me.